.
No, it's a 9-2-3-5-9-0-8-8-5.
Hi, my name is Srinath, I promise you are on duty for today.
How may I help you?
Hi, my feet are driving me crazy.
Can you give me something to fix it quickly?
Alright.
Okay, so before I provide you with any medications, it's alright if I ask you a few questions.
Okay.
Just to confirm, is this medications for you?
Yeah.
Alright.
Do you mind telling me your name, your age and also medical number?
My name is Naka.
I am 50 years old.
Medical number is URN 234567.
Alright.
Can you describe more about your symptoms?
Actually I would like to...
I would like to have some medication to fix my symptoms.
Actually the skin is red with cracking and peeling between the two toes.
Alright.
So did you notice any swelling or bleeding at affected area?
No.
Okay, no swelling.
May I know how long have the symptoms started already?
I think around 3 weeks.
3 weeks already.
Okay, so may I know?
Have you tried anything to relieve your symptoms?
No.
Okay.
May I know what might trigger the cause of your symptoms?
I'm not very sure, maybe because of the long working day in the Hudson.
Alright.
So, may I know are you kindly having any allergies?
I am allergic to peanuts.
That's okay.
May I know is this your first time experiencing this?
Yeah.
Okay.
Did you have any medical condition?
No, medical condition.
Did you consume any prescription medications?
No.
Any vitamins, supplements or anything?
Do you have any preference for your medications?
I prefer if it is a cream.
Cream, alright.
Do you mind giving me some time?
Did you answer information?
Sure.
All right, thank you for waiting.
So, from what you have said to me, you are actually experiencing Tanya, and the medication that I'm going to provide you is Clotrimazole Cream.
So, you can apply to the affected area two times daily, and continue for two weeks to prevent any reward infections, all right?
This medication is generally safe, but there might be some side effects, for example, like stingy and also burning sensations.
Other than that,
Try to change your socks frequently and also try the affected area with a separate towel.
Make sure that you do not share any towels with anyone as it can cause the infections to spread over yourself.
Is everything clear for you?
Do you have any questions for me?
Do you mind repeating back what I have to say?
I understood all the information given by you.
Alright, thank you.
So if the symptoms persist or the symptoms is worsening, you may come back again to the pharmacy or you may go to the doctor to check for a better diagnosis.
So here is the pamphlet about the tanya that you may look for about some information, okay?
Alright, I think that's all.
Thank you very much.
Okay.